Guide to the Alpha Delta Phi Records, 1832 - 2017
Alpha Delta Phi Records 1832 - 2017
- Series III: Chapter - Alpha Delta Phi - Middletown Chapter, 1856 -, 1856-2017
  - History
    - Wesleyan in the 1960s (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - 150th Celebration (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Halls & Houses (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Delta Phi remembers the 1930s1999 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Sesqui Oral Histories (Box 69, Folder 2)
      Contains DVDs.
    - Sesqui Oral Histories (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
  - Initiation Lists, imcomplete, 1986-2001 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Invitations (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Issues
    - Kitchen, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Summer Housing, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Liquor Permits, 2002-2014 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
  - Marriages (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Middletown Trustees (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Membership
    - Summary, 1861-1961 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - 2007 Spring (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Awards (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Female ADP, 1973-1991 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Certificates (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Directories (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Lists, 1956-2009 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
    - Lists - Officers (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - News stories, American Express Connections, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter
    - How to compile a newsletter (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Mailings (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Phi Forum, 1992-2014 (Box 71, Folder 7-9)
    - Alpha Delta Phi Newsletter, 1985-1992 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Alpha Delta Phi Newsletter, 1972-1984 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Alpha Delta, 1951-1968 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - The Emerald, 1925 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Officers
    - List (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Misc., 1982-2015 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - AdLit Chair (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Critic (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
    - Historian (Box 72, Folder 9-10)
    - House Manager (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - House Manager (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Poetry & Lit Chair (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - President
      See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - Yuhas, Eric
      - Manual (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Manual, outdated docs (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Notebook, 1991-1996 (Box 73, Folder 5-7)
      - Notebook, 1993-1996 (Box 74)
      - Notebook, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
      - Notebook, 1973-1991 (Box 76, Folder 1-3)
      - Files, 1984-1991 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Court, Alex, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Olsen, David, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Lichtenfeld, Eric, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Mazner, Jeremy, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Little, Nick, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - D'Arcy, Paul, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - D'Arcy, Paul (Mandatory Dining), 1992 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Recording Secretary
      - Roll Call, 1878 Spring-1920 February (Box 77)
      - Roll Call, 1926 May-1971 June (Box 77)
    - Retreat Chair (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Rush Chair
      - undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - undated (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
      - Pledge interviews of note for posterity (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Rush Manuals (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Pledge Manuals, 1992-1999 (Box 78, Folder 5-7)
      - Pledge Manuals, 2000-2007 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
      - Pledge Manuals, 2011-2015 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
      - Pledge Projects (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Pledge Projects, 1990 Fall, 2014 Spring (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
      - Pledging Lists (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer
      - 1997-2004 (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
      - Matthew Ruhlen, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - [1951?], 1978 June-1992 (Box 80, Folder 11-15)
      - Manual, 2012 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Vice-President, 1995-2006 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Personal Record Blanks, 1879-1913 (Box 82)
  - Personal Record Blanks, 1896, 1914-1934 (Box 83)
  - Personal Record Blanks, 1934-1951 (Box 84)
  - Personal Record Blanks, 1952-1965 (Box 85)
  - Personal Record Blanks, 1965-1973 (Box 86)
  - Personal Record Blanks, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
  - Plaques (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Relations
    - Handbook, 1974 May (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Reports (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Sesquicentennial Donor Honor Roll (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Sesqui Exhibit, 1950s-2000s (Box 81, Folder 8-12)
  - Star & Crescent
    - ALS Reports & Budgets (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence & Publicity (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Time Capsule
    - 2012-2017 (Box 81, Folder 15-18)
    - 2006-2012 (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
    - Historian-Raoul Doubleday, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      Contains DVD.
    - 2003-2005 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
    - Historian-Justin Rogers, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 1993-2002 (Box 88, Folder 4-11)
    - Oversize, 1990-2002 (Box 190)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
      Contains VHS.
    - 1989 Calendar (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
    - Argus clippings, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Quasimodal, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 1955-1987 (Box 90, Folder 3-10)
    - Photos & Argus articles, 1950s (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - 1949 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Photos, 1940s (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - 1871-1920s (Box 90, Folder 14-20)
  - Traditions
    - Axe Murderer (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Brunch Themes (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Competitions
      - Literary & Scholarship (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Literary & Scholarship, Essays (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
    - Consensus (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Elections (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Formal Meeting Procedures (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - House Room Names (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Housing Point Policy (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Quotes (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Senior Words & Top 10 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Symbolism (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Co-Education 1973-1991
  This series includes correspondence, histories, and newspaper clippings related to the debate to incorporate women members into the Alpha Delta Phi International. Materials for this series are housed in two document boxes, .83 linear feet.
  - History (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - undated, 1986-1991 (Box 91, Folder 15-21)
  - Kin Fung File, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - Polin, Jane
  - 1982-1985 (Box 91, Folder 23-26)
  - 1979-1981 (Box 92, Folder 1-3)
  - Agreement between ALS & Chapter, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - 1973-1978 (Box 92, Folder 5-10)
- Series V: House & Property 1856-2011
  This series contains the records related to the fundraising, purchasing, building, maintenance, and furnishing of both houses built by the Middletown Chapter, the first in 1884 and the second in 1904. Items found in this series include correspondence, architectural drawings, deeds, maps and mortgages. Materials for this series are housed in six document boxes and one oversize box, 5.5 linear feet.
  - Oversize, banners (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Oversize, blueprints (Box 191, Folder 11)
    See also Series V: House & Property - Renovations
  - Deeds (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Guest Registers, 1886-1989 (Box 93)
  - History
    - 1884 House
      - Construction specifications (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Description, A.W. Harris (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - 1884 House
    - 1884 Furnishing Committee; 47th Initiation; & 1884-1886 accounts with S.A. Taylor (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - 1877-1893 Building Fund donations (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - 1904 House (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - HVAC in Board Room, 1989-2001 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - House Insurance, 2016 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Mortgages
    - undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - ALS Loan from Wesleyan, 1984 September 20 (Box 94, Folder 3-4)
    - Mortgage release, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - $15,600, 1905 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - $500, 1895 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - $10,000, 1884 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Photos (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Removed to Series X: Photographs
  - Piano (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Postcards (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Property map: Alpha Delta Phi, 1931; Wesleyan, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Oversize, Property map: Alpha Delta Phi, 1931 (Box 191)
  - Property transactions
    - 1856-1929 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - History (Gershen) (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Renovations
    - Student kitchen, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Furnace warranty, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Front Porch Project
      - Waterfield Design invoices, contract, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Skynation invoices, contract, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Middletown, city of, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 19)
      - John Schukoski, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 20)
      - Contractors/bids, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 21)
      - Images/samples, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 22)
        Contains CD-roms
      - General file, 2005-2006 (Box 94, Folder 23)
      - Front Entrance Project, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - General file, 2000-2004 (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
    - Desks, bureaus, & chairs, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - BR/Hall project, 2003 Summer (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
    - Dumpster deal/new dumpster, 2002-2003 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - S&C, furniture & floor, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - 2000 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Greene Room egress, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 96, Folder 3-5)
    - Master Plan update, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Master Plan, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Budget & payroll, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 10-12)
    - Budget & payroll, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Bills, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Plans, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Lerner Room I. Jack, 1977-1979 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - 1974 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - House redecoration, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 6-7)
    - 1972 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Kitchen plan, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Harper project, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - 1933, 1955-1962 (Box 97, Folder 11-12)
  - Smoke detectors & smoking in the Grotto, 2011 January (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Series VI: International 1836-1992
  Includes constitution, correspondence, convention documents, officer handbooks, annual reports, visitation reports, publications and history. Materials for this series are housed in six document boxes, 2.5 linear feet.
  - Annual Report of Middletown Chapter, 1897-1972 (Box 97, Folder 14-20)
  - Chapter Letters, 1958-1987 (Box 98, Folder 1-9)
  - Chapter
    - Dartmouth (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - MIT, pledge manual, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Trinity (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Western (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Constitution, 1940 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Conventions
    See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - Wasch, William K. for missing Convention records.
    - 160th, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - 158-159th, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
    - Regional Conference @ Brown, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 157th, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - 152nd, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - 1982 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - 148-149th, 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 9-10)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 99, Folder 11-13)
    - 1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 141st, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - 1972 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - How to Run a Meeting, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - 134th, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 1965 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - 124th-132nd, 1956-1964 (Box 100, Folder 7-12)
    - 1947-1954 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - 1836-1926 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - Executive Council (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Handbook for Officers, 1958-1959, 1964, 1974, 1980 January (Box 101, Folder 5-7)
  - History (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Literary Competition
    - Announcements, 1968-1986 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Prize Winners, 1952-1988 (Box 102, Folder 3-7)
  - Perpetual Record, ca. 1872 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Tax exempt status of chapters, 1942 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Trademark infringement: Wrangler/Chi Delta Chi/ADP, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Visitation reports for Middletown Chapter (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Xaipe (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Ledgers 1899-1982
  This series contains the recordings of accounts for members, treasurers and the Star & Crescent Eating Club. These accounts were recorded in bound ledgers, with the exception of one folder of unbound ledger sheets. Materials for this series are housed in one document box and 15 oversize boxes, 9.4 linear feet.
  - Chapter
    - Member Accounts, 1899-1912 (Box 192)
    - Member Accounts, 1906/1907-1908/1909 (Box 193)
    - Member Accounts, 1909-1911 (Box 193)
    - Member Accounts, 1910-1914 (Box 194)
    - Member Accounts, ca. 1913-1915 (Box 194)
    - Member Accounts, 1917-ca. 1924 (Box 195)
    - Member Accounts, 1926-ca. 1935 (Box 195)
    - Member Accounts, 1917-1918 (Box 196)
    - Member Accounts, 1946-1950 (Box 196)
    - Member Accounts, 1952-1954 (Box 196)
    - Member Accounts, 1954-1957 (Box 196)
    - Member Accounts, ca. 1959-1961 (Box 197)
    - Member Accounts, ca. 1965-1967 & 1962-1964 (Box 197)
    - Member Accounts, 1966 (Box 197)
    - Member Accounts, 1967 December-1968 May (Box 197)
    - Officers
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1909-1912 (Box 198)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, October 1909-June 1916 (Box 198)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1907-1907 (Box 199)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1915-1917 (Box 199)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, petty cash, 1915-1917 (Box 199)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, Novemeber 1911-1918 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1919-1934 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, July 1938-June 1939 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, September 1938-April 1939 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1935-June 1938 & Member Accounts, 1935-1936 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1973-1976 (Box 200)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1940-1945 (Box 201)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, petty cash 1945-1946 (Box 201)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1945-1948 (Box 201)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1948-1950 (Box 201)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, ca. 1962-1974 (Box 202)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1968-1970 (Box 202)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1958-1960 (Box 203)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1960-ca. 1965 (Box 203)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1962-1965 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Treasurer's Accounts, 1974-1982 (Box 203)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1907-1910 (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1908-1910 (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1912-ca. 1913 (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, [ca. 1914?] (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, [1915-1916] (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1918-1919 (Box 204)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1919-1920 (Box 205)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1920-1921 (Box 205)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1934-1938 (Box 205)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, [1933-1936] (Box 206)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1952-1958 (Box 206)
  - Star & Crescent Eating Club, 1954-ca. 1957 (Box 206)
- Series VIII: Members, 1852-2011
  This series contains records related to or of undergraduate or after graduate members and includes AEF, ALS and Chapter related records of officers; correspondence; article clippings; newspaper clippings; postcards; pins; a scrapbook; and realia. The Vertical File sub-series contains materials that were collected by those other than the named individual and may have been added to over a period of time. The Personal Papers sub-series consists of materials created and organized by the named individual, most of whom are past ALS Presidents. Materials for this series are housed in 65 document boxes and three custom or oversize boxes, 32 linear feet.
  - Vertical File
    - Alpha Phi Fraternity Club [of New York City], ca. 1900 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Ames, William, 1933 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Andrus, John Emory, 1862 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Barlow, John Perry, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Beebe, Richard Knowles, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Beebe, William Hammond, 1938 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Biddle, Michaelle L. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Blakemore, Bill, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Browning, Dominique, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Bruner, Clark (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Bucy, Kara, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Cameron-Scorsese, Domenica (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Chamberlain, Joshua (Bowdoin), 1852 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Davison, George W., 1893 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Deininger, Nicholas, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Dickson, Paul, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Di Lello, Chiara, 2011 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Dunn, Jeff, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Edgerton, Charles Sherman, 1870 (Architect of the 1884 ADP House) (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Espy, Ridgway Bowers, Jr., 1943 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Follett, Foster Valentine, 1925 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Fraser, Laura, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Gerrard, Ian (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Gershon, Robert D., 1974 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Goldberg, Julie, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Goldsmith, Stuart, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Gram, Harvey B, Jr., 1927 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Green, Mitchell K., 1953 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Greene, Richard Leighton (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Oversize, Greene, Richard Leighton (Box 207)
    - Griffin, John H, Jr., 1938 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Gudebrod, George David, 1931 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Gui, Wei Hsin, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Hargens, Gar (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Harris, Abram Winegarden, 1880 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Henry, Rodney D., 1957 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Hunting, Peter Morse, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Jackson, Andrew, 1937 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Johnston, Albert Wheeler, n1892 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Kaminsky, Stephen R., 1987 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Konerding, Erhard (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Krovatin, Christopher, 2007 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Lee, Beck (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Lemkau, Charles William, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - Leonard, William, 1878 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Levy-Spira, Eduardo (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Littell, Frank Bowers, 1891 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Realia - Littell, Frank Bowers.
    - Little, Nicholas, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Lowe, Samuel H., 1976 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Ludlum, Robert, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Maloney, William Bailey, 1933 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - McKelvey, Robert G., 1959 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - McKelvey, Robert G.
    - McNicol, Frederick Bones, 1927 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Mercado, Andrea (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Meredith, Christopher, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Charles M., 1947 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Philip Sheridan, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Oat, Donald L., 1947 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Ott, Norman E., 1948 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Oviatt, Clifford R, Jr., 1949 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Parsons, George Raymond, Jr., 1959 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Pickett, Kate, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Pickett, William Howard, 1943 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Pitt, Louis Wetherbee, 1915 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Prosise, Kim, 2011 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Roberts, David A., 1958 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Robson, Robert Kenneth, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Roth, Michael S., 1978 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Roth, Michael S., 1978 (Box 207)
    - Rozbicki, Stephen Richard, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Schalk, Ellery Stowell, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Scott, Charles, Jr., 1886 & Scott, John Bell, 1881 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Stevens, Joshua Power, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Stoner, Andrew, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Swain, Christopher, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Swain, Joseph R, Jr., 1925 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Taormino, Tristan, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Taylor, Joseph Harrington, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Titus, David (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - Vasiliou, William (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Wasch, William K., 1952 (Box 104, Folder 35)
      See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - Wasch, William K.
    - Weber, John-Alexander Gordon (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - West, Richard A., 1956 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Yuhas, Eric, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 38)
      See also Series VIII: Members - Personal Papers - Yuhas, Eric.
    - Zarfos, Kristen (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - Personal Papers
    - Arnold, Herbert A.
      Herbert A. Arnold served as a board member of the ALS and was Chairman of the Scholarship Committee. His files span from 1980-1991.
      - AD General, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      - AEF General, 1982-1984 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      - AD General, 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - AEF General, 1987-1990 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, Johnson
      Johnson Cooper served as Chairman of Membership & Alumni Records Committee for the ALS. His records range from 1974-1982.
      - 1974-1977 (Box 105, Folder 4-5)
      - 1977-1982 (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
    - Coulombe, Susan
      - Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 4)
        These records cover Coulombe's time as Historian for the Chapter.
      - International (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Pledge (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Alumnae Relations (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Rush (events) (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - For the Books (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - S and C (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - ALS (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - AEF (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - ALS stationery (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Star-N-Crescent (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Sports (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Artsy ADP (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Literary-ness (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Assembly (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Music series (Box 107, Folder 12)
      - Music at ADP (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Prose series (Box 107, Folder 14)
      - Film series (Box 107, Folder 15)
      - Coffeehouse (Box 107, Folder 16)
      - Social (Box 107, Folder 17)
      - Faculty Fellows (Box 107, Folder 18)
      - Co-Ed (Box 107, Folder 19)
      - Wesleyan (Box 107, Folder 20)
      - Awards (Box 107, Folder 21)
      - Officers Manuals (Box 107, Folder 22)
      - House (Box 107, Folder 23)
      - ADP Middletown Chapter stationery (Box 107, Folder 24)
      - Historian (Box 107, Folder 25)
      - Policy (Box 107, Folder 26)
      - Fraternities at Wesleyan (Box 107, Folder 27)
      - 1989-1996 (Box 107, Folder 28)
      - 1989-1996 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Flannigan, E. Jenny K.
      The files of Jenny Flannigan cover her tenure as President of the ALS from 1996 October 19 - 2002 June, include the First Society Annual Convention which was hosted by the Middletown Chapter and document the extensive and major renovations to the Chapter House. Jenny also served as a board member of the AEF. These files span from 1992-2003.
      - AEF
        - 1996 (Box 108, Folder 2)
        - 1998 (Box 108, Folder 3)
        - 6/1999 (Box 108, Folder 4)
        - 2000 (Box 108, Folder 5)
        - 2001-2002 (Box 108, Folder 6)
        - AEF/ALS Lease, 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 7)
        - AEF/ALS Lease, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 8)
        - AEF/ALS Lease, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 9)
        - 1930s project, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 10)
        - 1930s videos, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 11)
          Contains VHS videotapes.
        - AEF/Writer's Conference, 1999, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
      - ALS
        - Banquet in Honor of Robert G. McKelvey, 1997 May 30 (Box 109, Folder 3)
        - Board & Mailing list, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 4-5)
        - Chapter relations, 1996-2002 (Box 109, Folder 6-10)
      - AEF & ALS
        - Meeting Agendas & Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1-2)
      - ALS
        - Meeting & Notes, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 3-4)
        - Meeting Agenda & Correspdondence, 1996 July 27 (Box 110, Folder 5)
        - Meeting Agenda & Minutes, 1996 October 19 (Box 110, Folder 6)
        - Meetings, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 7-12)
        - Meetings, 2000-2002 (Box 111, Folder 1-2)
        - Trustee Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Alumni/Alumnae Relations
        - 25th Anniversary of Coeducation at Alpha Delta Phi (Box 111, Folder 4)
        - 1998-2002 (Box 111, Folder 5-8)
      - Finance
        - Email, 2000-2002 (Box 112, Folder 1)
          Contains CD-Rom.